♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro Is the Emperor=
=Episode 22=
(The Best Pavilion in the World)
Hey,
this is so boring.
I'm about to fall asleep.
How about
a little match?
Sure.
Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Night show, get ready.
(The Best Pavilion in the World)
Music.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend♪
♪Of our own♪
Protect His Majesty!
Quick!
I'll kill you!
I'll go after the Princess Royal.
Gu Bei!
Gu Bei.
- Your Majesty.
- Gu Bei!
Gu Bei.
Summon the imperial physician!
Wake up.
- Summon the imperial physician!
- Gu Bei!
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
Your Majesty,
Official Gu's poison
is extremely deadly.
If we can't find the antidote...
What if there's no antidote?
I have an antidote from the plains.
This...
It should cure him.
- Gu Bei.
Gu Bei.
Help him sit up.
Imperial physician, take another look.
How is he?
His pulse has stabilized.
The medicine neutralized
most of the poison,
but what's left
has seeped deep into his body.
If it isn't purged soon,
Official Gu's life
will be in danger.
Your Majesty,
please save my brother.
The Princess Royal
must have the antidote.
No matter where she is,
I'll find her.
Wait.
Imperial physician,
didn't you just say
that if the poison
can be expelled,
he'll survive?
That's right.
No.
I've had enough.
I'm leaving.
Your cold isn't getting better.
A good steam
will help sweat the toxins out.
I have an idea.
It's worth a try.
Gu Bei,
a man only dies once.
You've already died once.
You don't get another chance.
Wake up now.
Do you hear me?
Gu...
Gu Bei.
Gu Bei?
Are you awake?
If you don't wake up,
I'll sell
Xiaoyao Pavilion.
I'm serious.
You can take my life,
but don't you dare sell Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Whatever it takes,
you must deliver the message.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Bei,
how do you feel right now?
I feel completely refreshed
after that sleep.
Xiao,
you saved my life.
No, your Xiaoyao Pavilion did.
I told you.
A good steam flushes out the poison.
Have you found the Princess Royal?
We've searched the whole city.
She's nowhere to be found.
She has joined forces
with Western Yi.
Their fifty thousand troops
are already outside the capital.
I've sent my shadow guards
to deliver my orders to every commander,
calling them to the capital
to capture the usurper.
Then we'll hold the city
until reinforcements arrive.
It won't be that easy.
The nearest army
is over 500 li away.
Even if they ride day and night,
it'll take at least seven days.
If
the Western Yi attacks,
we can hold out
for only three days.
Xiao,
I've got an idea.
What's it?
Let's run.
A wise man knows when to retreat.
Staying alive comes first.
Besides, we're rich now.
We can just pick a place
and start over, can't?
Run?
Where would I go?
Come with me to the frontier.
Or back to the plains.
We can take
Gu Nan and Xiao Ling.
If you want,
you can bring
all your consorts too.
What about them?
Who?
The people of Jing.
What will they do?
The Princess Royal sold Fushou Cream
to poison her own people
for the throne.
If she becomes emperor,
what will become of the realm?
And what can you do by staying?
Can you hold the capital?
Bei,
if I'm not wrong,
you hated history class,
didn't you?
What are you trying to get at?
You think history can save you?
No.
But it taught me
what it means to be a ruler.
"The emperor guards the frontier,
a king dies with his nation."
Even if I don't belong to this era,
I still have a duty to fulfill.
I hate violence.
But now
I have no choice.
Because I'm the Emperor.
Alright.
My good Emperor.
Then we'll die together.
Maybe if we both die,
we'll wake up back in modern times.
If you're staying,
I'm staying too.
No.
You have to leave.
I'm entrusting
those dear to me to your care.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪